<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Eugene Dobrovolsky</title>
    <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Eugene Dobrovolsky</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives 2014-20XX</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_0/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domesting</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_1/</guid>
      <description>domesting.com↗︎  This is a previewMore detailed info and images coming soon.  
Domesting develops mobile and web based platform that connects users to commercial and residential cleaning companies. The platform allows users to find and book services for domestic cleaning, cleaning of communities, office cleaning, cleaning of the commercial premises, cleaning in educational centers, garage cleaning, and industrial cleaning and sanitation.
I was at Domesting for about 6 months from almost the very beginning doing branding, UI/UX, front-end, print and just like it often happens in startups trying to help the ream succeed in every way I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Agenda</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_5/</guid>
      <description>firstagenda.com↗︎ App Store↗︎  This is a previewFull case study coming soon.  
The average employee spends 37% of their work time in meetings. When those meetings are ineffective, that adds up to a lot of wasted time and money.
At FirstAgenda, we have taken a stand against unproductive meetings by developing the digital meeting solutions Prepare and Assistant. Our focus is to optimize all stages in the process of preparing for, organizing and following up on meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripopotamus</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_2/</guid>
      <description>This is a previewFull case study coming soon.  
Tripopotamus is a travel agency for each and every one. Searching for travel today is a time consuming process. Using our dynamic packages’ platform allows to reduce the time of package formation considerably. The platform is going to be experience oriented, budget-aware and will allow combine and countercheck different means of transportation and several destinations.


Unfortunately, Tripopotamus didn&#39;t make it, but I personally learned a lot from it, so it was totally worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velvet Ropes</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_3/</guid>
      <description>velvetropes.com↗︎  This is a previewFull case study coming soon.  
Velvet Ropes is a revolutionary development combining celebrity homes, hot spots and sightings into one easy-to-use app for people who love all things celebrity. Velvet Ropes was created to fill a massive void - an easy way to navigate celebrity homes, find celebrity hot spots and report &amp;amp; search real-time celebrity sightings! There are four &amp;quot;Star Maps&amp;quot; being sold in Los Angeles alone claiming to be &amp;quot;updated regularly&amp;quot;, but we found all 4 maps have completely different addresses for the same person in many cases - not to mention how out-dated paper maps are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiredrive Go</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_4/</guid>
      <description>wiredrive.com↗︎App Store↗︎ Coming soonCheck out the links above.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>