<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eugene Dobrovolsky</title>
    <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eugene Dobrovolsky</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 14:03:54 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, my name is Eugene</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 14:03:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>History Its started out as a hobby when I got into print design and typography. So, I took a course in graphic design and learned the basics of color, composition, typography, and how to apply it in branding. Then, around 5 years ago, I got obsessed with web design and took a quick course on Treehouse. Shortly after that I started doing it for a living, but over the course on the next few years I gradually transitioned into UI/UX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/about/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 17:12:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/about/colophon/</guid>
      <description>This is not my first personal website. After a few years of having one that I updated maybe 2 or 3 times in a year I realized what I had was a bit of an overkill.
My previous website was made on Wordpress and hosted on Mediatemple which cost me 20$/month + 15$/year for the domain + throwing in 50$/year Typekit subscription, which is optional, but it was the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My workflow</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/posts/post_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 17:15:04 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/posts/post_1/</guid>
      <description>This post is largely about Product Design. If you are not sure what it is exactly, Eric Eriksson has your back with What is Product Design?. In a sentence, it’s about understanding the problem, designing a solution, shipping it and iterating until it solves the problem. It’s quite brief, so, in a way, it is just another boring sketches and mockups iteration article of which there’s a good number on Medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domesting</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_1/</guid>
      <description>domesting.com↗︎  
Domesting is a web based platform that connects users to commercial and residential cleaning companies. The platform allows users to find and book services for domestic cleaning, cleaning of communities, offices, commercial premises, garages, and just about every other kind of cleaning and sanitation.

I was at Domesting for about 6 months from almost the very beginning doing everything: branding, UI/UX, front-end, print, etc. Just like it often happens in startups we were all trying to help the team succeed in every way we could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Agenda</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_5/</guid>
      <description>firstagenda.com↗︎ App Store↗︎  This is a previewFull case study coming soon.  
The average employee spends 37% of their work time in meetings. When those meetings are ineffective, that adds up to a lot of wasted time and money.

FirstAgenda has taken a stand against unproductive meetings by developing the digital meeting solutions Prepare and Assistant. Their focus is to optimize all stages in the process of preparing for, organizing and following up on meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tripopotamus</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_2/</guid>
      <description>Tripopotamus was to be a one-stop-shop web travel platform that would allow to combine different components to create one&#39;s own perfect vacation.
Research shows that the path to purchase is complex, and traveler search activity is intensifying, an average customer making 32.5 visits to 10.3 websites before the order. Tripopotamus wanted to simplify this process believing that you need to spend less time on planning trips and more enjoying it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Velvet Ropes</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_3/</guid>
      <description>velvetropes.com↗︎  
Velvet Ropes is a digital multi-platform star map and a regularly updated source that you can depend on for only the best information about your favorite celebrities.
Velvet Ropes was created to fill a void - an easy way for people who love all things celebrity to navigate Hollywood for celebrity homes, hot spots and sightings that are combined in a one easy-to-use app.

How it started I joined in spring 2016 for a little under a year and was responsible for design and direction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wiredrive Go</title>
      <link>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://eugenedobrovolsky.com/works/work_4/</guid>
      <description>wiredrive.com↗︎App Store↗︎ 
Wiredrive is a cloud content management and collaboration solution for marketing and production teams.
I was called in to revamp the iOS apps and tasked to mainly focus on the UX and make sure the iPhone and the iPad app function perfectly. I just followed Apple&#39;s design guidelines and made all designs very close the those of iOS system apps.
How it started There already were functioning apps on both iPhone and iPad, but they were lacking in good UX and aesthetic of the interface.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>